Today again, I say here’s to this wonderful world
Laughter erupting all over the city
Pretend not to look, it’s all fake
About to lose my mind
An alluring scent that makes me lightheaded
Stimulates my nose
Wakes me up instinctively
Whose turn is it today?
What can be done in this world?
What can I do?
Just want to make sure that from those pitch-black eyes
Tears won’t fall
For a better future, again and again
I keep grasping
In this world full of wrong
I want you to smile
Don’t want to hurt anyone anymore
Want to be strong, strong
So I can stay true to myself
Today again, this wonderful world is safe
Bad rumors swirling in the city
Turned a blind, blind eye and looked away
It’s pure madness
People dressed up dead seriously for a march
Footsteps that lead to
With a taste so overpowering, never to disappear, disappear
The other side of the world
To live a good and honest life
To live without causing any sorrow
To stay on the straight and narrow, no missteps
Is that how you live without making mistakes?
Is justice about living as you are or
Is justice about faking through life
Need to know what I should be
Who is my true self?
Tell me
Once again today
In a world with no answers
I hope
Though I may be awkward
Just together with you, forever
If want to keep laughing so
My heart skips a beat and
Rocks my body yelling
It’s time to move right now
The weakling that I am, over and over
I try to overcome
In this world full of wrong
I want you to smile
So no one will have to cry anymore
Want to be strong, strong
So I can stay true to myself
Just so I can protect you
I run, run, run
I’ll overcome “me” that lives inside of me